早上好 阳光少女
Good morning, sunshine.
昨晚在院子里睡得怎么样
How was your night in the yard?
完美 我就喜欢睡在外面
Perfect. I like sleeping outside.
海莉又弄丢了钥匙
Haley lost her keys again.
她在经历不负责任的阶段
She's been going through this irresponsible phase.
是啊 长达25年了
Yeah, for 25 years.
我不会让她持续到26年
I'm not gonna let her get to 26.
我要说明一点 克莱尔不会杀了她
Just to be clear, Claire's not going to kill her.
让我进去 拜托
Let me in! Please!
-不 -拜托
- No. - Please?
就像她小时候我们对她用费伯入眠法一样
This is just like when we Ferberized her as a baby.
让她哭够了就会安静下来
Let her cry it out. She'll settle down.
为什么啊
Why?!
我扔一条毛毯出去怎么样
What if I just throw a blanket out there?
有我们味道的东西
Something that smells like us.
你们怎么能留我在外面 现在是凌晨两点啊
You can't leave me out here! It's 2:00 in the morning!
我得换衣服参加派对啊
I have to change for a party.
晚安 亲爱的
Good night, honey.
-早上好 菲尔 -不要
- Morning, Phil. - No!
今天不...
It's not a --
不是什么好早晨
It's not a good morning.
而且今天接下来还会更糟糕
It's gonna be an even worse day.
每天早上我洗澡之前 都会踢起内裤
Every morning, before I shower, I kick off my underwear.
如果我接到了 今天就会很棒
If I catch it, it's gonna be a great day.
如果没有
If I don't...
不
No!
那就是灾难
...disaster.
我知道这听起来很神经病
I know that sounds crazy,
但这是我家族流传的传统
but it's an old family ritual
我祖父一直这样做 直到他去世那天
my grandfather did until the day he died --
那天... 你猜到了
a day -- you guessed it --
那天他没接到内裤
that he dropped his underwear.
我也不知道怎么回事
I don't know what happened.
那一踢力道强劲
It was a strong kick,
脚踝的摆动恰到好处
ankle flick was on point.
这只是个荒唐的迷信
It is just a ridiculous superstition.
荒唐吗 我们来回顾往事
Ridiculous? Let's review.
我滑旱冰撞上蜜蜂的那天
The day I Rollerbladed into bees --
我没接到内裤
I dropped my underwear.
我滑旱冰撞上营火的那晚
The night I Rollerbladed into that campfire --
不如你别滑旱冰吧
How about you stop Rollerblading?
不如我别呼吸了
How about I stop breathing?
我没接到内裤的日子 最好的选择就是
When I miss my catch, the best thing I can do
在安全的地方等待今天过去
is just wait it out in a safe place.
今天不行 不不不
Unh-unh. Not today. No, no, no.
我们有一大堆家事得处理
We have a ton of errands to get done
然后下午要去看斯迪利·丹乐队
before we go see Steely Dan this afternoon.
-那是几点 -下午三点
- What time is that? - ?3:00 P.M.
-为什么这么早... -他们不年轻了 菲尔
- Why is it so -- - They are not young men, Phil.
真棒 我手机坏了 这全怪你们
Great. My phone is broken, and it's your fault.
这黑锅从何而来
How do you figure that?
因为我昨晚得朝松鼠扔手机
Because I had to throw it at some squirrels last night
来阻止它们攻击我
to keep them from attacking me.
你们得给我买台新手机
You guys have to buy me a new one.
破财 霉运开始来了
Costing me money. It's already happening.
没有 你没破到财
No, it's not costing you money
因为我们才不给她买新手机
because we are not buying her a new phone.
什么
What?!
但我工作时要用手机
But I need it for work.
我得坐在白痴高尔夫球场中一整天
I sit on a stupid golf course all day.
不看手机我还能看什么
What else am I supposed to look at?
等你买得起新手机
You can have a new phone
你就能拥有新手机了
when you can afford a new phone.
菲尔 你能把贝果切了放去烤吗
Phil, would you cut and toast those bagels?
让我用刀吗
With the knife?
亲爱的 这是备用钥匙
Sweetie, here are the spare keys.
你再去给我配一份
I would like you to make yourself a copy.
我都等不及知道你会怎么弄丢下一副了
I can't wait to find out how you lose those.
难怪邻居觉得你很刻薄
No wonder the neighbors think you're so mean.
睡在外面什么都听得见
You hear everything when you sleep outside.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria!
我刚去车库了
I was just out in the garage.
你有什么想告诉我的吗
Is there anything you want to tell me?
有
Uh, yes.
我扔掉了你的健身器械
I got rid of your exercise machine.
那个根本就是垃圾
It was a piece of junk.
你欠我和动作演员查克·诺里斯一个道歉
You owe me and Chuck Norris an apology.
但我说的是你车上的凹痕
But I'm talking about the dent in your car.
你撞到的是无伤大雅的东西
Did you hit something we can talk about,
还是我得拿水冲掉证据
or should I hose the front
然后找一家不多问问题的修车厂呢
and find a body shop that doesn't ask questions?
我没撞到东西
I didn't hit anything.
一定是我跟乔在商店时
Someone must have hit me
别人撞到我的车
when I was inside the store with Joe.
既然聊到了意外
But talking about accidents,
如果你的狗再敢尿在我的一只拖鞋里
if your dog pees one more time in one of my slippers,
我也许会意外
I may accidentally
把她忘在某个海滩上
leave her at the beach.
我不会让这种事发生的
I would never let that happen.
干嘛朝她撒气
And don't lash out at her.
如果你撞车了
If you crashed the car,
告诉我就好
just tell me.
我没有
I didn't.
我也不喜欢被人说我撒谎
And I don't appreciate being called a liar.
你不是吧 你每次都打死不承认错误
Are you kidding? You can never admit to making a mistake
我简直会被你气死
and it drives me crazy.
还记得我们的印第安纳州罗马市之旅吗
Remember that romantic trip we took to Rome, Indiana?
我本来就是计划去那里啊
That's where I wanted to go.
我没买错机票好吗
I meant to buy those tickets.
那你为什么学意大利语
Then why did you learn Italian?
妈妈咪呀 杰
Mamma mia, Jay.
如果我真出了车祸
If I had been in an accident,
我会承认的
I will admit it.
现在我要去网上买更多拖鞋了
Now, I have to go and buy more slippers online.
尽量别让电脑崩溃[撞]了
Try not to crash the computer.
小卡 健身房的毛巾小妹
Hey, Cam. So, the towel girl at the gym
说我看起来像是老版哈里王子
said that I look like an old Prince Harry.
你不是吧 你又在偷听小帕了吗
Oh, come on. Are you eavesdropping on Pam again?
我在努力听 但你一直在旁边吵
Yes. I'm trying to, but you keep talking.
她在打电话
She's on the phone.
亲爱的 我也想你
Oh, baby, I miss you, too.
如果你在这里 你不会相信...
If you were here, you can't believe...
不不 太恶心了
No. No. Okay, that's just gross.
-那可是你姐姐 -嘘
- That's your sister. ?- Shh.
我会对你做什么
...things I'd do to you.
我知道你只有10分钟
I know you only got 10 minutes...
10分钟 他还有时间限制吗
10 minutes? He's on a time limit?
她在跟监狱里的博说话
She's talking to Bo in jail.
博是小帕孩子的爸爸
Bo is Pam's baby daddy --
目前被关在密苏里州的格拉斯霍普
currently incarcerated back in Grasshopper, Missouri,
他朝警马的脸上打了一拳
for punching a police horse.
现在 我担心
And now, I'm worried
她会放弃自己的未来
she's just gonna throw her future away by
回到他身边去
getting back together with him.
真受不了她别的时候都很坚强
It's crazy how weak she is with him
只要一跟他一起就秒变弱鸡
when she's so strong in other ways.
她可是三届乡村集市拉骡子大赛的冠军啊
I mean, she is the three-time winner of the country-fair mule drag.
别偷听了 小卡
Step away from the pipe, Cam.
别这样 你没这么没出息吧
Come on. You're better than that.
我就是这么没出息 你也一样
No, I'm not, and neither are you.
我们看电影《BJ单身日记3》的时候
You eavesdropped on that couple
你还偷听坐我们后面的情侣呢
behind us at "Bridget Jones's Baby."
不 我那不是偷听
Oh, no, that wasn't eavesdropping.
那里是公共场所好吗
We were in public.
你以为我还真想听
And do you think I really wanted to hear
那个白痴复述的第一部情节吗
that moron's recap of the first movie?
何况一半的细节还说成别部电影的
Half those details were from "Love Actually."
你以为我就喜欢这样吗
Do you think I'm happy about this situation?
我恨不得完全听不到她说话呢
I wish I couldn't even hear her at all!
老板 你偷听完你姐姐说话了吗
Hey, Boss, are you done listening to your sister?
兄弟们想知道他们能不能用台锯了
The boys are asking if they can use the table saw again.
好吧 他在开玩笑
Okay, well, he's joking.
佛朗西斯科做包工头之前
Before Francisco was a contractor,
曾经在危地马拉讲单口相声
he did stand-up comedy in Guatemala.
不止在危地马拉
Not just in Guatemala.
其实我这周五晚上还要讲个10分钟的...
Actually, I'm doing 10 minutes this Friday night at the --
我们订好餐厅了
Oh, we have dinner reservations.
-基佬节日 就是... -对啊
- Oh, gay holiday. Yeah, um... - ?Yeah.
你走之前我想跟你说一下这个水槽
So, look, but I do want to talk about the sink before you leave.
抱歉 米奇 木已成舟
Sorry, Mitch. That ship has sailed.
还有 你有带灶台防溅墙的新瓷砖来吗
Oh, also, did you bring the new tiles for the backsplash?
有啊 在我车里 我马上回来 老板
Yes, they're in my truck. I'll be right back, Boss.
太好了 拿过来吧
Great. Okay. Yeah. Go get those.
我不想小题大做
Hey, um, I-I don't want to make a big deal about this,
但你有注意到他叫你"老板" 但叫我"米奇"吗
but do you notice how he calls you "boss" and me "Mitch"?
没有 但是我有注意到
No, but I did notice
他工具腰带上其中一个小袋子
...how one of his little pouches on his tool belt
装满了软心糖豆 多可爱啊
is filled with jelly beans. How cute is that?
重点是 他把你当成是真正的老板
The point is, he treats you like the actual boss
而把我当成像神经病花瓶妻子
and me like I'm some, you know, ditzy trophy wife.
首先 我们不是同意过
First of all, I thought we agreed
我们家的情况是罕见的花瓶双娇吗
we had the rare dual-trophy-wife situation.
-是啊 -除此之外
- Yeah. - ?And aside from that,
还可能是因为我更坚定有主见一些
maybe it's because I'm a little more, you know, assertive.
你这么认为吗 其实我也想过这个
Do you think so? Because I actually have thought that.
我觉得我可能太被动了
I mean, maybe I'm too passive,
-这可能是我事业停滞不前... -不
- which could be why my career has stalled... - ?No.
以及我曾三次同意跟女人上床的原因
...or I agreed to have sex with all three women who asked me.
-好吧 -那感觉好温柔...
- Okay. - ?Oh, it was so gentle...
又好恶心
?...and gross.
你知道吗 现在你的机会到了
You know what? Well, now's your chance.
你可以向佛朗西斯科展示你才是大佬
You can show Francisco that you're the big dog.
重点是肢体语言 知道吗
It's all about body language, okay?
向他展示你能领导一切
Show him you can lead the pack.
我来了 老板
Here you go, Boss.
告诉我你最喜欢哪一个 可以吗
Let me know which one you like best, all right?
等我们决定了 会告诉你的
Well, when we decide, we will let you know.
但是首先 我想先来谈谈洗碗机的事儿
But first, I wanted to talk about the, uh -- the dishwasher.
我说了要放在左边
Uh, I wanted it over here on the left,
但不知为何 你把它放在右边了
but now, for some reason, it's on the right.
我要你按我要求的把洗碗机放在左边
I would like it on the left like I asked.
听懂我的主张了吗
Asserted?
不不不 眼睛 眼睛看这里 好吗
No, no, no, no. Eyes -- Eyes over here, okay?
这事儿我说了算
This -- This is my thing.
给你看个东西
Well, let me show you something.
-好 -你看看水池下面
- Yeah. ?- All right, look under the sink.
没问题
Will do.
蹲下去 到最下面
Go down. All the way.
好了 现在钻到里头去
Okay, now, get in there.
抬头看 你看到你左边的管子了吗
Look up. Do you see that post on your left?
等等 好了
Wait. Ho-- Okay.
我无法挪动那玩意儿
I can't move that,
所以洗碗机只能放在现在这个位置
which is why the dishwasher needs to stay where it is.
还有别的问题吗
Anything else?
没有 我没事
No, I'm good.
衣服上沾到了一些木屑
Got some sawdust on your shirt.
很痒啦
It tickles.
孩子 醒醒
Hey, kid. Wake up.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
怎么了
What?
你妈的车撞了个大坑
Your mom's car got a big dent in it.
我知道你当时和她在一起
Now, I know you were with her.
你看到事情经过了吗
Did you see how that happened?
肯定是我们在店里时 有人撞到我们车了
Someone must have hit the car when we were in the store.
那是你老妈说的
That's what your mom said,
但如果有其他原因 比如说...
but if it was something else, like, I don't know,
她出了点小事故 你也可以告诉我啊
she got into a little fender bender, you could tell me.
肯定是我们在店里时 有人撞到我们车了
Someone must have hit the car when we were in the store.
我知道她先跟你通气了 但是...
I know she got to you, but, uh...
我要你跟我说实话
I need you to tell me the truth.
这冰激凌是给我的吗
Is that ice cream for me?
有可能
Could be.
你妈的车到底是怎么回事
What happened to your mom's car?
我可以等一整天
I can wait all day,
但是问题是冰激凌是会融化的
but the trouble with ice cream is, it melts.
我喜欢融化的冰激凌
I like it when it melts.
什么叫你喜欢融化的冰激凌
What do you mean you like it when it melts?
没人喜欢融化的冰激凌
Nobody likes ice cream when it melts.
就像汤一样
It's like soup.
你讨厌喝汤啊
You hate soup.
不讨厌巧克力汤
Not chocolate soup.
听着 我们都跑题了
Look, we're getting off track here.
跟我说说你妈的车到底怎么回事
Tell me what happened to your mom's car,
我就把冰激凌给你
and you can have your ice cream.
你好啊 杰
Hello, Jay.
歌洛莉亚 我...
Gloria, I...
瞧瞧你
Look at you,
还想贿赂一个五岁的小孩子
trying to bribe a five-year-old.
丢死人了你
You should be ashamed.
走吧 乔 既然你醒了
Let's go, Joe. Now that you're awake,
妈咪给你弄健康的零食
Mommy's gonna fix you a healthy snack.
查她手机
Check her phone.
看她的手机
把冰激凌留下
And leave the ice cream.
等我回来就刚好全化了
It'll be nice and warm when I get back.
菲尔 你能不能换一下楼下厨房的灯泡
Oh, Phil, could you change the lightbulb down in the kitchen?
你先是让我帮忙清洁纱窗
First you ask me to help clean the window screens.
现在让我去做爬梯子和接触电源这种高危工作
Now you want me to do something with a ladder and electricity?
你忘记我内裤的事了吗 克莱尔
Have you forgotten about my underwear, Claire?
我有些朋友的老公人很差劲
Look, I have friends whose husbands are mean
或酗酒 或根本不回家
or drink too much or don't come home at all.
然而在那一刻 我羡慕死了那些朋友
And in that moment, I envied those friends.
好吧 我自己去厨房换灯泡
Fine. I will change the lightbulb in the kitchen.
你可以把这些柔软蓬松无害的衣服放好
You can put away this nice, soft, fluffy laundry.
-好的 -别担心
- All right. - ?Don't worry.
里面连拉链和纽扣都没有
There's not even any zippers or buttons.
没有任何尖锐的东西
Nothing sharp in there.
我可不想害你出什么叠衣断指意外
Wouldn't want you to lose a finger in a tragic folding incident.
我在放好那些安全无害的衣服时
I was putting away that harmless laundry
踩到了卢克的滑板
when I stepped on Luke's skateboard,
从卸了纱窗的窗口滑了出去 掉到了树篱里
rolled out the screenless window, and landed in the hedge.
不过你说得对
But you're right.
我很肯定这跟我的内裤没任何关系
I'm sure it had nothing to do with the underwear.
这是自我应验
It's self-fulfilling.
菲尔坚信会有坏事发生
Phil believes something bad is gonna happen,
所以他主动让坏事发生
so he makes it happen.
被纸割伤了
Ow! Paper cut.
今天当然会这么衰了
Of course, today.
不是吧你
Seriously?
这也是内裤预言的一部分吗
Is this part of the underwear prophecy?
你会不会戏太多了
Aren't you being a little dramatic?
菲尔
Phil?
这件事就有点难解释了
Little bit harder to connect the dots on that one.
但巧合时有发生嘛
But coincidences do happen.
老公 没事的
Honey, it's fine.
哪天你接住内裤了 我们再把事办完
We'll just finish our errands on a day when you catch your underwear.
演唱会票在你那儿吗
Oh, do you have the tickets?
在车里 但我还是别开车了
They're in the car, but I don't think I should drive.
行吧 但回家你来开
Fine, but you are driving home,
因为今天我要买醉
because today, I'm reelin' in the wine.
钥匙在你那儿 抛给我吧
Oh, you've got the keys. Can you toss them to me?
好的 给 不
Yeah, here. No!
不 那是我们的钥匙 快停车
No! Those are our keys! Stop!
有人想去看斯迪利·丹乐队 上帝冷笑
Man plans to go to Steely Dan. God laughs.
靠 备份钥匙在海莉那里
Damn it. Haley has our other set of keys.
对 克莱尔 我真觉得被松鼠咬了
Yes, Claire, I do think it bit me a little!
歌洛莉亚 抱歉
Gloria, I'm sorry.
你是我的妻子
You're my wife.
我爱你 信任你
I love you, and I trust you.
跟反社会分子讲道理是行不通的
You can't reason with a sociopath.
你得通过示好来诱骗他们
You lure them with kindness.
让他们以为你们在同一阵线
You lull them into thinking you're on the same side,
然后用确凿的证据逮住他们
and then nail them with incontrovertible evidence,
而我已经掌握了证据
which I had.
我还发现 我在她的通讯录里仍然叫
I also found out I'm still listed in her phone
"穿红色运动服的那个杰"
as "Jay, Red Tracksuit."
你说你没撞车 我就相信你
If you say you weren't in an accident, I believe you.
谢谢老公
Thank you, baby.
不过还有一件事
There is just... one more thing.
那是我的手机吗
Is that my phone?
是的 你手机里有很多有趣的照片
Yeah. You've got a lot of interesting pictures here,
但这张尤其有趣
but especially this one.
看起来像是你的车头
It looks like the front end of your car
撞上了这辆车的车尾
is rammed into the back end of this car.
我不是什么保险理算员
Now, I'm not an insurance adjuster,
但我觉得这可以算是证明
but I would say that that's pretty solid proof
你撞了车的铁证啊
you were in an accident.
那不是我的车
That's not my car.
那你为什么会拍别人车祸的照片呢
But why would you take a picture of some random accident?
用来提醒自己生命有多宝贵
To remind me of how precious life is.
那是你的车牌号
That's your license plate.
你知道车牌都是什么人做的吗 杰
Do you even know who makes license plates, Jay?
囚犯
Prisoners!
你宁愿信一个重刑犯的话
Are you gonna take the word of a convicted felon
也不信你老婆吗
over your wife's?
-毫无道理 -正是
- Makes no sense. - ?Exactly.
你到底有什么毛病
What is your problem?!
你看不出这对我有多闹心吗
Don't you see what this is doing to me?!
我得知道你犯错时能承认错误
I need to know that you can admit when you made a mistake.
我知道你心中还有一点善 歌洛莉亚
I know there's good in you, Gloria!
给
Here you go.
我... 真是对不起
I -- I am so sorry.
好好珍惜它
Cherish this.
这是有手机以来 我首次那么久没碰手机
It was the longest I've been without a phone since phones.
一开始很难适应 大拇指抽搐
It was hard at first -- the twitching thumbs,
总觉得有震动 没被发到朋友圈的沙拉
the phantom vibrations, salads left un-Instagrammed.
但之后发生了很奇妙的事
But then the strangest thing happened.
你们有停下脚步闻过这些花吗
Have you ever stopped to smell these things?
我好多年都没在现实生活中大笑过了
It's been years since I LOL'd IRL.
我还在车上找到一本旧书 开始读了起来
I even found an old book in the truck and started reading it.
唯一的问题是 总被人打断
The only problem was, people kept interrupting.
我不再需要手机了
I didn't need a phone anymore.
我只需要找到安静的地方
I just needed a quiet place to find out
来看他们是如何杀死那只知更鸟的
how they kill that mockingbird.
不好意思
Hey, excuse me.
Excuse me!
抱歉打断你抛光 佛朗西斯科[音似旧金山]
S-Sorry to bother you while you sand, Francisco, um --
真有意思
Oh, that's cute.
我想再看一下给橱柜选好的油漆颜色
I just want to revisit the paint color we chose for the cabinets.
旧色板你还有吗
Do you still have the old sample?
-也许吧 我去看看 -好的
- Uh, maybe. I'll go look. - ?Okay.
你和老板商量过了吗
Did you discuss this with, uh -- with the boss?
-我不必问... -二爸 大爸在哪儿
- I don't have to discuss it with -- - Daddy, where's Daddy?
你需要什么
Oh. Yeah, what do you need?
-我的行李箱 -为什么
- My suitcase. ?- Why?
我要和特里西娅一家去迪士尼
I'm going to Disneyland with Tricia's family.
宝贝女儿 我已经帮你收拾好行李箱了
Sweetie, I already packed your suitcase.
他肯定给我打包了太多鞋
Ugh, there's gonna be too many shoes.
我们几时决定了莉莉可以去迪士尼玩
When did we decide that Lily could go to Disneyland?
我们不是说好要商量这事吗
I thought we were gonna talk about this.
她只会缺课一天而已
She's missing one day of school.
我五年级时缺了一半的课 因为被猪咬了
I missed half of the fifth grade because of a pig bite,
而我的教育程度还是和其他人一样啊
and I'm just as educated as anyone else.
是吗 我们刚认识时 你以为你在中美洲长大
Really? When we met, you thought you grew up in Central America.
密苏里就是在美国[美洲]中部啊
Missouri is in the center of America.
好吧 你还认为是穴居人把恐龙杀光了
Okay. You also thought that the cavemen killed the dinosaurs.
-你亲眼看过不是这样吗 -重点是
- Were you there? - Okay, t-the point is,
我们应该一起做这些决定
we should be making these decisions together.
你要的是这个颜色吗
Is this the one you wanted?
-是的 -为什么又拿那个来
- Yes. - ?What's that doing back in here?
我想重新看一下本来的油漆颜色
I just wanted to revisit the original paint color.
好的
Oh, okay.
-有主张 -很好
- Asserting. - ?Good.
有主张
Asserting.
好吧
Okay.
我能和你聊两句吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
你们两个为什么说悄悄话还笑了
Uh, what's up with the whispering and the laughing?
他刚刚讲了个笑话
He just made a joke.
笑话我吗
At my expense?
不 是笑话他老婆厨艺不好
No, it was about his wife's cooking,
但肯定比他讲笑话的水准强
which can't be as stale as his material.
你这是怎么了
What's this about?
莉莉的事你就跟我先斩后奏 现在我担心
You undermined me with Lily, and now I'm worried that
你又和佛朗西斯科搞起了这一套
you're doing the same thing with Francisco.
米奇尔 我们是同一战线的
Mitchell, we are on the same team here. ?
我们都想要一间漂亮的厨房
We both want a beautiful kitchen,
-我们也都想尽快完工 -是的
- and we both want it done as soon as possible. - ?Yes.
活都停下
Stop working!
-别钻了别钻了 -我真想和你在一起
- Drills down! Drills down! - I want you so bad.
如果我伸出手就能摸到你该多好
If only I could reach out and touch you.
别再偷听了
Enough with the eavesdropping.
-够了 -没错 你知道吗
- Come on. - ?Yeah. You know what?
如果这没救的家伙又要跟博复合
If that little train wreck's getting back together with Bo,
那我就要直接出手
I need to deal with this directly.
不 你不许去
No, you have to stay here -- Ugh.
帕梅隆·杰西卡·塔克 你给我听好
Pameron Jessica Tucker, listen to me.
从这一刻起
You need to stop those dirty
不许你再往监狱里给博打情色电话
jailbird phone calls right this second with Bo,
-否则我... -我的天啊
- or I am -- ?- Oh, my God!
你一直在偷听我的私人通话吗
You've been listening in on my private conversation?
你真该为自己感到羞耻
You should be ashamed of yourself.
打电话时像蟋蟀镇的姑娘那么恬不知耻
Talking like a girl from Cricketsville --
咱家不是这么教育你的
you were raised better than that.
你少管我的事
You stay the hell out of my business.
也少瞧不起蟋蟀镇
And stop looking down your nose at Cricketsville.
人家现在也有连锁百货了 门外还有搬钱机
They got a Target now with a Banksy on the side of it.
才怪 我才不信涂鸦大师班克西
Yeah, right. I'm sure Banksy
会亲自开车去蟋蟀镇到超市旁边去画...
drove to Cricketsville and painted on the s-
你指的是自动提款机
Oh, you mean the ATM.
不然我还能指什么
Well, what the hell else would I be talking about?
你好 我叫卡梅隆·塔克
Hi, my name is Cameron Tucker,
我想与你们的一位犯人通话
and I would like to speak to one of your inmates.
他的名字是博·约翰逊
His name is Bo Johnson.
萨莉·梅·詹金斯
Sally Mae Jenkins?
我当然记得你 其实呢...
Oh, of course I remember you! Oh, wait, but --
我一点也不惊讶你在监狱做接线员
I'm not surprised you're answering phones at a prison.
你的声音一直是中美洲第一好听的
You always had the prettiest voice in Central America.
你居然给博打电话吗
You called Bo,
你这个大山一样的白痴
you ginormous mountain of stupid?!
没错 我打了
Yeah, that's right, I did.
我告诉他你在这和你的宝宝
And I told him you were getting your life together here
慢慢步上正轨 不许他再来烦你
with your baby and he needed to back off.
他根本不知道我生了他的孩子
He didn't even know I had his baby.
-什么 -现在他知道我在哪了
- What? - ?Now he knows where I am.
他出狱后会来找我的
He's gonna come looking for me when he gets out!
你把一切都毁了 你这个大马脸蠢材
You ruined everything, you giant, horse-faced dummy.
为什么损我的每一句话都要加"大"字
I'm not sure why every insult needs a size component.
我真的很抱歉
Look, I'm really sorry.
我不知道你不是在和博打电话
I had no idea that wasn't Bo on the phone.
那还有谁能让你用那么"亲密"的语气说话
Who else would you be so... intimate with?
任何愿意出三美元一分钟听我说荤话的人
Anybody who can pay three bucks a minute for nasty talk.
你是色情电话的接线员吗
Okay, you're a phone-sex operator?
我当素人模特根本不能糊口
My real-person modeling gigs haven't been paying the bills.
我需要一份能留在家陪孩子的工作
And I needed a job where I could stay at home with the baby.
我都不知道现在还有人打色情电话
I didn't even know that still existed.
现在不都有手机应用和网络了吗
Like, I thought it was all apps and the Internet now.
不是每个人
Not everyone leads
都过着你这种海滨小资生活 小卡
your coastal-elite lifestyle, Cam.
这个国家里满是正直辛劳的美国人
There's a whole country full of decent, hardworking Americans
仍旧喜欢对着电话撸管
who still want to torque their doolies on the phone,
你个庞大的势利眼
you gargantuan snob!
你只骂"势利眼"不行吗
Just could've said "snob."
少自恋了 我是在画树
Oh, get over yourself. I'm drawing the tree.
-杰 -我打电话你不接
- Jay? ?- I tried to call you.
你的手机呢
Where's your phone?
留房间里了
It's in my room.
我现在身在创作的空间里
I'm in a creative space right now.
她很可爱
She's cute.
我和你妈间有点事拎不清
I'm going through a little something with your mom.
我想听听你的看法
I need your take on it.
我等不及和你一起侵犯他人隐私了
Hm. I'm excited to see what boundaries we cross here.
她开车出了起小事故
She had a little fender bender.
我也提出了确凿的证据
I've got her dead to rights --
-但她就是不认错 -没错
- And she won't admit it. ?- Yes.
她从不承认错误
She never admits when she's wrong.
谢谢你 我都开始觉得是我有问题了
Thank you. I was beginning to think I was the crazy one.
是啊 她有这本事
Yeah, she'll do that to you.
就因为她不承认丢了我收藏的剧场节目单
I got IBS when she refused to admit that she threw out
我得了肠易激综合征
my collection of playbills.
我就当你说的是"流感"和《花花公子》吧
I'm gonna pretend you said "the flu" and Playboys and move on.
我想我 蛮怀念你还在家时
I guess I... miss you being around
在她行为乖张时能陪我一起翻白眼
to share that eye roll when she gets kooky.
我一直以为你是冲我翻白眼
I always thought you were rolling your eyes at me.
也有那种时候
Well, that, too.
但能娶到她 忍这些也值得吧
At least she's worth it, right?
绝对的
Definitely.
她后来承认扔节目单的事了吗
So, did she ever cop to the Playbills?
你猜怎么着
You know what?
最后真承认了 但只因为她犯了更大的错
Yeah, eventually, but only because she did something worse.
其实这样挺好的
?It's actually a good thing.
只要她还不承认出了事故
As long as she's denying the accident,
你就知道她没犯其他更大的错
you know that's the worst thing she's done.
谢了 孩子
Thanks, kiddo.
既然你来了 我遇到了些问题
Hey, while you're here, I wouldn't mind picking your brain
想听听你的建议
about a little problem I'm having --
是我笔下的一个角色
Well, one of my characters.
他正站在人生的岔路口
He finds himself at a crossroads --
别破坏这美好的一刻了
Let's keep this special.
歌洛莉亚 我一直在想
Gloria, I've been thinking.
关于那起小事故 我不会再提了
That whole accident thing? I'm dropping it.
你说没那回事就没那回事
You say it didn't happen, it didn't happen.
有那回事
It happened.
什么 你现在要承认吗
What, are you admitting it?
是的 那起事故是我的错
Yes. The accident -- it was my fault.
求你原谅我 亲爱的
Please forgive me, mi amor.
斯黛拉哪去了
Where's Stella?
-还有 佛朗西斯科 -怎么 老板
- And, Francisco... - Yeah, Boss?
我想我们该再考虑一下
...I guess we should take another look
米奇尔重新提起的这个橱柜颜色
at this cabinet color Mitchell revived from the dead.
为公平起见 我们在厨房的光线下看看
To be fair, let's look at it in the kitchen light.
想象一下我在娱乐宾客
So, imagine I'm entertaining.
我在烹饪 在客人面前妙语连珠
I'm cooking. I'm throwing out delightful quips to my guests.
老实说 会不会显得我没精神
Be honest -- does it wash me out?
的确会显得我没精神
It washes me out.
我辛辛苦苦爬上爬下
These are the kind of conversations
就为了聊这种鬼话吗
I snuck under the fence for?
这个好笑吗 是我的段子啦
Hm? ?Is that funny? Oh. ?It's in my act.
我... 我还有另一个段子
It's... I also do this bit, though,
是说我去木场然后遇到个辣妹...
where I go to a lumberyard and I meet this hot girl and --
好啦 我得先请你打住
Okay. I'm gonna stop you right there.
如果最终笑点是跟"硬起来"的木头有关
If the punch line has anything to do with wood,
我觉得你没差到需要用三俗哏
you're better than that.
没错 我宁愿被葬入墙中
Yes, I chose to be entombed in a wall
也不愿意跟小卡承认我偷听他
rather than admit to Cam that I was eavesdropping.
是的 我也意识到婚姻咨询
And, yes, I realize couple's counseling
或许可以再考虑一下
should be back on the table.
米奇尔想要的这颜色...
This color Mitchell wants...
感觉你不喜欢
You don't seem to like it.
的确是不太喜欢 但他喜欢 那就这个吧
I don't love it. But he does, and let's just go with it,
因为... 我想要他开心
'cause it -- I want to make him happy.
我老婆估计问都不会问我
Wow. My wife wouldn't even ask me.
你人真好 跟你在一起他很幸运
You're very nice. He's lucky to have you.
相信我 我才是幸运的那个人
I'm the lucky one, trust me.
我俩每一天都是从这个厨房开始 我...
You know, we start every morning off in this kitchen, and I --
我想要我俩步入这里时
I want us both to walk in here
都能看到自己所爱的东西
and see something we each love.
有啊 我有看到我所爱的
I do! I-I do see something I love!
那就是你啊
It's you.
米奇尔
Mitchell! ?Oh.
什么鬼...
What in the he--
你刚才在偷听我
You were eavesdropping.
我错了 但我还是坚持我那句话
I'm sorry. I-I stand by what I said.
偷听是不对的
Eavesdropping is wrong.
我 我应该自己问佛朗西斯科
I-I should have just asked, uh, Francisco myself.
为什么你叫他"老板"却叫我"米奇"
W-Why is it you call him "boss" and me "Mitch"?
没事 你直说吧 我能承受
It's okay. You can tell me. I-I can take it.
因为我记不得他的名字
Well, uh, I can't remember his name.
-什么 -是吗
- What? ?- Really?
我一直想叫"小康"
You know, I keep wanting to say "Krang,"
但我知道他名字不是这样
but I know that's not right.
还是其实就是这个
Unless it is?
-是小卡 -是小卡
- It's Cam. ?- It's Cam.
我们天天见面了这么多天啊 佛朗西斯科
Okay. We have spent every day together, Francisco.
我有点生气啊
I'm a little offended.
那这话听完你可能会消点气
Oh. Well, if it makes you feel any better,
我的名字其实是佛南多
my name's actually Fernando.
的确是消了气
Oh. ?It does help.
她在那里
Ah! There she is.
海莉
Haley!
-海莉 -要命啦
- Haley! - Oh, my God!
这是什么鬼
What is going on?!
靠 没有那钥匙不行啊
Damn it! We need those keys!
我们得在演唱会
Got to get to the concert before the roadies
他们选辣妹去后台派对前就到场啊
pick all the hot chicks that get to party backstage.
我有点迷糊了
I'm confused.
-哪怕是当年 他们也不.... -海莉
- Even back in the day, they weren't exactly... - ?Haley!
这样吧 我去跟她取
You know what? I'll go get them.
不 别 不许你去
No. No. You can't.
今天不许
Um, not today.
你也相信诅咒 对吧
You believe in the curse, don't you?
我也搞不懂啊
I don't understand it.
可是你今天一直像衰神附身
Bad things have been happening to you all day.
或许...
Maybe...
或许就是那内裤在搞鬼
Maybe it's the underwear.
我... 我不能冒这个险
I just -- I can't take a chance.
-你待在这吧 -不行不行不行
- You stay here. - No, no, no, no, no.
能发生在我身上最糟糕的事
You getting hurt is the worst possible thing
就是我的宝贝老婆受伤
that could happen to me. ?
告诉孩子们我爱他们
Tell the kids I love them.
亲爱的
Oh, honey.
你... 你没穿胸罩吗
Are you, uh -- Are you not wearing a bra?
好吧 那你小心点
All right, be safe.
我的老天
Oh, my God.
那人是邓菲
That's Dunphy.
第一个打中他的人赢50块怎么样
50 bucks to the first guy who hits him, huh?
开始
Go.
海莉
Haley!
爸
Oh, Dad?
好的 听我说
Okay, listen.
我的车钥匙丢了 我需要你那份备用的
I lost my car keys. I need the spare set.
我知道我这样算说一套做一套
I know that makes me a hypocrite.
你完全有权生我的气
But you have every right to be angry with me.
有这么多该感恩的事情 我怎么会生气
How could I be angry when there's so much to be grateful for?
那个... 是书吗
Is that a -- a book?
多亏你没给我新买手机 我才有幸读到它
I never would have picked it up if you had bought me a new phone.
你长了点白头发 我喜欢
You've gotten a little gray. I like it.
宝贝 给我钥匙
Honey...the keys?
对不起 刚才被这些黄蜂给分散心思了
Sorry. I was distracted by those bumblebees.
你听 它们在互相交流呢
Shh, listen -- they're talking to each other.
是贱人格尔吗
Is that freakin' Gil?
爽 爽爽爽
Yes! Yes, yes, yes!
这程度的事每天都可能发生
Well, that could happen any day.
还没死 让暴风雨来得更猛烈一些
He's still moving! Machine-gun him!
用最快速度连发
Just hit as fast as you can!
天啊 他这是要我亲命啊
Dear God! He's got me dialed in!
早安啊 两位
Morning guys.
你们错过了美好的日出
You missed a beautiful sunrise.
这几天所度过的无手机生活
You know, living without a phone these past few days
简直像上天的恩赐
has been such a gift.
所看到的颜色更鲜艳了
Colors are brighter.
尝到的味道也更美味
Tastes are tastier.
你们吃过桃子吗
Have you ever eaten a peach?
我是指真的品尝过桃子
I mean really eaten a peach?
大多数我都写在我的短文里了
Well, most of it is in my short story.
但最棒的部分 是我真正地认识了你们
The best part though, is really getting to know you two.
老爸 你真的好有趣
Dad, you are so funny.
你还有最温暖的目光
You have such kind eyes.
老妈 你是一个衣柜公司的董事长
And mom, president of a closet company?
太厉害啦
Way to go!
所以分别也变得好艰难
I guess that's why it makes so hard to say goodbye.
今早到的 卢克帮我设置好了
Came in this morning. Luke set it up for me.
他真的长大了呢
He really shot up huh?
总而言之
Anyway.
在接下来的日子里
In the weeks to come,
尽量记得...
try and remember that...
这臭婊子
That skank!
别想
No way!